// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What approximate value should come in place of the question mark (?) in the following equation? 158.25 x 4.6 + 21% of 847+?= 950.93 50 45",
    answer: "45",
    options: [
      "35",
      "45",
      "75",
      "85"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What should come in place of the question mark (?) in the following equation? 9548+7314=8362+?",
    answer: "8500",
    options: [
      "8230",

      "8500",

      "8410",

      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is incorrect for Fabaceae?",
    answer: " Actinomorphic flower",
    options: [
      "Actinomorphic flower",
      "Monocarpellary superior ovary",
      " Vexillary aestivation",
      "Legume fruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: " If the arithmetic mean of 6, 8, 10. x, 7 is 8.the value of x will be",
    answer: "9",
    options: [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "If an infinite GP has the first term x and the sum 5, then which one of the following is correct?",
    answer: "x < - 10",
    options: [
      "– 10 < x < 0",
      "x < - 10",
      "0 < x > 10",
      "x > 10"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " A nucleus of uranium decays at rest into nuclei of thorium and helium. Then?",
    answer: "The helium nucleus has more kinetic energy than the thorium nucleus",
    options: [
      "The helium nucleus has more kinetic energy than the thorium nucleus",
      "The helium nucleus has less momentum than the thorium nucleus",
      "The helium nucleus has more momentum than the thorium nucleus",
      "The helium nucleus has less kinetic energy than the thorium nucleus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Haversian canals occur in?",
    answer: "Humerus",
    options: [
      "Scapula",
      "Humerus",
      "Clavicle",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Where A’ is the transpose of A. 5. If A, B and C are subsets of a Universal set, then which one of the following is not correct?",
    answer: "A ∪ (B ∩ C) = (A ∪ B) ∩ (A ∪ C)",
    options: [
      "A ∪ (B ∩ C) = (A ∪ B) ∩ (A ∪ C)",
      "A’ ∪ (A ∪ B) = (B’ ∩ A)’ ∪ A",
      "A’ ∪ (B ∪ C) = (C’ ∩ B)’ ∩ A’",
      "(A ∩ B) ∪ C = (A ∪ C) ∩ (B ∪ C)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Major inorganic components of vertebrate bone is",
    answer: "calcium phosphate",
    options: [
      "Potassium hydroxide",
      "Calcium phosphate",
      "Calcium carbonate",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "A person travels 10 km North and 20 km East. What will be the displacement from the initial point?",
    answer: "22.36 km",
    options: [
      "20 km",
      "22.36 km",
      "30 km",
      "32.36 km"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];